<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CitiEST</string>
    <string name="title_activity_weather">weather</string>
    <string name="title_activity_my_events">MyEvents</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_event">AddEvent</string>
    <string-array name="city_names">
        <item>Tallinn</item>
        <item>Tartu</item>
        <item>Narva</item>
        <item>Pärnu</item>
        <item>Viljandi</item>
        <item>Rakvere</item>
        <item>Võru</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="city_introductions">
        <item>Tallinn is the capital of Estonia and is home for almost one third of the population.
            It is located in the northern part of the country on the shore of Gulf of Finland of the Baltic sea.
            Tallinn\'s Old Town is one of the best preserved medieval cities in Europe and is listed as a UNESCO World Heritage Site.
        </item>
        <item>
            Tartu is the second largest city in Estonia and is often considered the intellectual centre of the country as
            it is home to the nations oldest and most renowed university, University of Tartu. It is also the birthplace of Estonian Song Festivals. Tartu lies
            on the Emajõgi ("Mother River"), which connects the two largest lakes of Estonia.
        </item>
        <item>
            Narva is located at the eastern extreme point of Estonia, at the Russian border, on the Narva river which drains Lake Peipus.
            It is the third largest city in Estonia with 95.7% of the population being native Russian speakers.
        </item>
        <item>
            Pärnu is the fourth largest city in Estonia. It is located in the southwestern Estonia on the coast of Pärnu Bay.
            It is the most popular summer holiday resort with many hotels, restaurants and large beaches. The majority of tourists visiting Pärnu are
            Finns, Swedes and Russians.
        </item>
        <item>
            Viljandi is located on the shore of Lake Viljandi and is considered to be the cultural capital of Estonia, partly
            due to the Viljandi Culture Academy being located there. The largest music festival with a focus to European folk music called Viljandi Folk Music Festival
            is held in Viljandi annualy in the end of July.
        </item>
        <item>
            Rakvere is a town in northern Estonia. It is believed to be the smallest city in Europe to have a professional
            theatre, that has given Estonia many famous actors. It is also known for the Vallimägi hill that holds the largest animal
            statue in the Baltic coutries, Tarvas.
        </item>
        <item>
            Võru is a town in southern Estonia. It is the home for Võru Folklore Festival, which has been held since 1995 annualy.
            Near the city in the Võru county, the highest peak of Estonia, Suur Munamägi (The Big Egg Hill) is located, reaching
            318 metres above the sea level.
        </item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="Tallinn">
        <item>Freedom Square,59.4338522,24.7439242</item>
        <item>Kohtuotsa viewing platform,59.437748,24.741744</item>
        <item>Tallinn Town Hall,59.4370026,24.7452927</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Tartu">
        <item>Tartu Kaarsild Bridge,58.380747,26.726262</item>
        <item>Tartu Dome Church,58.3802096,26.7144597</item>
        <item>AHHAA Science Centre,58.3762162,26.7336465</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Narva">
        <item>Kreenholm island,59.3577882,28.1884671</item>
        <item>Narva Town Hall,59.3793778,28.1965383</item>
        <item>Narva Museum,59.3754105,28.1989267</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Pärnu">
        <item>Pärnu beach,58.3716442,24.5002603</item>
        <item>St. Elizabeth\'s Church,58.3838028,24.4979112</item>
        <item>Pärnu scenic camping track,58.3731382,24.5083207</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Viljandi">
        <item>Viljandi Fortress and castle hill,58.358615,25.5925859</item>
        <item>St. John\'s Church,58.3610367,25.5905963</item>
        <item>Swing with the best view over Viljandi,58.3610231,25.5999884</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Rakvere">
        <item>Bull statue,59.3491399,26.3507648</item>
        <item>Rakvere Castle,59.3481158,26.3518495</item>
        <item>Turu Square,59.3480956,26.36114</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Võru">
        <item>Võru main square,57.8450889,26.99489</item>
        <item>Tamula beach,57.8438755,26.9879447</item>
        <item>Katariina Church,57.8485636,26.9929205</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
